= My Sweet Professor= =Episode 12=
= أستاذي الحلو = = الحلقة 12 =
Gao Yuan.
جاو يوان.
You have to eat some brocoli.
عليك أن تأكل بعض البروكلي.
It's good for your waist and kidneys.
إنه جيد لخصرك وكليتيك.
You said you hurt your waist, right?
قلت إنك تؤذي خصرك ، أليس كذلك؟
Come check it if you have time.
تعال للتحقق من ذلك إذا كان لديك وقت.
It's getting late.
الوقت يتأخر.
We should go,
علينا الذهاب،
and let Gao Yuan take a good rest.
ودع Gao Yuan تأخذ قسطًا جيدًا من الراحة.
I'm a little drunk.
أنا مخمور قليلا.
I won't go home.
لن أذهب إلى المنزل.
I'm staying here.
أنا باق هنا.
I'll find a designated driver.
سوف أجد سائق معين.
Huo Shang, where do you live?
هوه شانغ ، أين تعيش؟
I'll ask the driver to send you home.
سأطلب من السائق أن يرسلك إلى المنزل.
What driver?
أي سائق؟
Live here. Let's all live here.
يعيش هنا.  دعنا نعيش جميعا هنا.
My place is too small for you guys.
مكاني صغير جدًا بالنسبة لكم يا رفاق.
Don't steal the bedroom from me.
لا تسرق غرفة النوم مني.
Mm. I'm going up.
مم.  انا اتقدم.
Here it is then.
ها هو ذا.
These two places
هذين المكانين
are gonna be ours from now on.
ستكون لنا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Our places?
أماكننا؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Huo Shang.
هوه شانغ.
Here.
هنا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Look.
نظرة.
He plays so well.
يلعب بشكل جيد.
Who's he?
من هو؟
Qi He. Our senior.
تشى هي.  كبار لدينا.
He's repeating a year of school.
إنه يعيد سنة دراسية.
He's very nice. He helps me a lot.
انه لطيف جدا.  هو يساعدني كثيرا
Gao Yuan.
جاو يوان.
You can play Gobang too.
يمكنك لعب Gobang أيضًا.
Yes, a little.
نعم قليلا.
Let's play a round.
لنلعب جولة.
OK.
نعم.
Huo Shang.
هوه شانغ.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
You're not gonna study with me?
أنت لن تدرس معي؟
I'm not.
أنالست.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I'll help you with your lessons.
سوف أساعدك في دروسك.
No need. I have things to do.
لا حاجة.  لدي أشياء للقيام بها.
Mm.
مم.
I...
أنا...
I gotta go.
أنا سأذهب.
Bye.
وداعا.
Hey, where's Huo Shang?
مهلا ، أين هوه شانغ؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
How could you not know it?
كيف لا تعرفه؟
You guys are always together.
أنتم يا رفاق دائمًا معًا.
He just abandoned me suddenly.
لقد تخلى عني فجأة.
Then go ask him why.
ثم اذهب واسأله لماذا.
Will you just go?
هل ستذهب فقط؟
(Huo Shang)
(هوه شانغ)
You go first. I have things to do.
اذهب أولا.  لدي أشياء للقيام بها.
Then I'm gonna go, bye.
ثم سأذهب ، وداعا.
= My Sweet Professor=
= أستاذي الحلو =